<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<terms>
    <!-- PREDICATES -->
    
    <!-- kPREDICATE_SUBCLASS_OF -->
    <term kTAG_LID="SUBCLASS-OF" kTAG_NAMESPACE="">
        <kTAG_KIND>
            <item>:KIND-PREDICATE</item>
        </kTAG_KIND>
        <kTAG_LABEL language="en">Subclass of</kTAG_LABEL>
        <kTAG_DEFINITION language="en"><![CDATA[This predicate indicates that the
        	<i>subject of the relationship</i> is a <i>subclass of the object of the
        	relationship</i>, in other words, the <i>subject is derived from the object</i>.
            ]]>
        </kTAG_DEFINITION>
        <kTAG_SYNONYMS>
            <item>kPREDICATE_SUBCLASS_OF</item>
        </kTAG_SYNONYMS>
	</term>
    
    <!-- kPREDICATE_SUBSET_OF -->
    <term kTAG_LID="SUBSET-OF" kTAG_NAMESPACE="">
        <kTAG_KIND>
            <item>:KIND-PREDICATE</item>
        </kTAG_KIND>
        <kTAG_LABEL language="en">Subset of</kTAG_LABEL>
        <kTAG_DEFINITION language="en"><![CDATA[This predicate indicates that the
        	<i>subject of the relationship</i> represents a <i>subset of the object of the
        	relationship</i>, in other words, the <i>subject is contained by the object</i>.
            ]]>
        </kTAG_DEFINITION>
        <kTAG_SYNONYMS>
            <item>kPREDICATE_SUBSET_OF</item>
        </kTAG_SYNONYMS>
	</term>
    
    <!-- kPREDICATE_ATTRIBUTE_OF -->
    <term kTAG_LID="ATTRIBUTE-OF" kTAG_NAMESPACE="">
        <kTAG_KIND>
            <item>:KIND-PREDICATE</item>
        </kTAG_KIND>
        <kTAG_LABEL language="en">Attribute of</kTAG_LABEL>
        <kTAG_DEFINITION language="en"><![CDATA[This predicate indicates that the
        	<i>subject of the relationship is an attribute of the object of the
        	relationship</i>, this means that the subject of the relationship is a
        	<i>feature</i>.
            ]]>
        </kTAG_DEFINITION>
        <kTAG_SYNONYMS>
            <item>kPREDICATE_ATTRIBUTE_OF</item>
        </kTAG_SYNONYMS>
	</term>
        
    <!-- kPREDICATE_METHOD_OF -->
    <term kTAG_LID="METHOD-OF" kTAG_NAMESPACE="">
        <kTAG_KIND>
            <item>:KIND-PREDICATE</item>
        </kTAG_KIND>
        <kTAG_LABEL language="en">Method of</kTAG_LABEL>
        <kTAG_DEFINITION language="en"><![CDATA[This predicate relates <i>method
        	vertices</i> with <i>feature vertices</i> or <i>other methods</i>, it indicates
        	that the subject of the relationship is a <i>method, or workflow variation</i>
        	of the object of the relationship. This predicate is used to connect the
        	<i>pipeline of modifiers</i> applied to a <i>feature vertex</i>.
            ]]>
        </kTAG_DEFINITION>
        <kTAG_SYNONYMS>
            <item>kPREDICATE_METHOD_OF</item>
        </kTAG_SYNONYMS>
	</term>

    <!-- kPREDICATE_SCALE_OF -->
    <term kTAG_LID="SCALE-OF" kTAG_NAMESPACE="">
        <kTAG_KIND>
            <item>:KIND-PREDICATE</item>
        </kTAG_KIND>
        <kTAG_LABEL language="en">Scale of</kTAG_LABEL>
        <kTAG_DEFINITION language="en"><![CDATA[This predicate is used by <i>scale
        	vertices</i> to <i>connect feature or trait vertices</i>, the subject of the
        	relationship represents a <i>scale or unit</i> and the predicate indicates that
        	the object of the relationship uses that scale or unit. This predicate is
        	specifically used to indicate the different scales in which a feature or trait
        	vertex can be expressed in.
            ]]>
        </kTAG_DEFINITION>
        <kTAG_SYNONYMS>
            <item>kPREDICATE_SCALE_OF</item>
        </kTAG_SYNONYMS>
	</term>
    
    <!-- kPREDICATE_ENUM_OF -->
    <term kTAG_LID="ENUM-OF" kTAG_NAMESPACE="">
        <kTAG_KIND>
            <item>:KIND-PREDICATE</item>
        </kTAG_KIND>
        <kTAG_LABEL language="en">Enumeration of</kTAG_LABEL>
        <kTAG_DEFINITION language="en"><![CDATA[This predicate relates <i>vertex
        	elements</i> of an <i>enumerated set</i>, it indicates that the subject of the
        	relationship is an <i>enumerated set element instance</i>. If the object of the
			relationship is also an enumerated set element instance, this means that the
			subject is a subset of the object.
            ]]>
        </kTAG_DEFINITION>
        <kTAG_SYNONYMS>
            <item>kPREDICATE_ENUM_OF</item>
        </kTAG_SYNONYMS>
	</term>
    
    <!-- kPREDICATE_PREFERRED -->
    <term kTAG_LID="PREFERRED" kTAG_NAMESPACE="">
        <kTAG_KIND>
            <item>:KIND-PREDICATE</item>
        </kTAG_KIND>
        <kTAG_LABEL language="en">Preferred choice</kTAG_LABEL>
        <kTAG_DEFINITION language="en"><![CDATA[This predicate indicates that the object of
        	the relationship is the <i>preferred choice</i>, in other words, if possible,
        	one should use the object of the relationship in place of the subject. This
        	predicate will be used in general by <i>obsolete or deprecated items</i>.
        	The scope of this predicate is similar to the <tt>VALID</tt> predicate, except
        	that in this case the <i>use</i> of the subject of the relationship is <i>only
        	deprecated</i>, while in the <tt>VALID</tt> predicate it is not valid.
            ]]>
        </kTAG_DEFINITION>
        <kTAG_SYNONYMS>
            <item>kPREDICATE_PREFERRED</item>
        </kTAG_SYNONYMS>
	</term>
    
    <!-- kPREDICATE_VALID -->
    <term kTAG_LID="VALID" kTAG_NAMESPACE="">
        <kTAG_KIND>
            <item>:KIND-PREDICATE</item>
        </kTAG_KIND>
        <kTAG_LABEL language="en">Valid choice</kTAG_LABEL>
        <kTAG_DEFINITION language="en"><![CDATA[This predicate indicates that the object of
        	the relationship is the <i>valid choice</i>, in other words, the <i>subject of
        	the relationship is obsolete or not valid</i>, and one should use the object of
        	the relationship in its place. This predicate will be used in general to store
        	the obsolete or deprecated versions. The scope of this predicate is similar to
        	the <i>PREFERRED</i> predicate, except that in this case the use of the
        	<i>subject of the relationship is invalid</i>, while in the <tt>PREFERRED</tt>
			predicate it is only deprecated.
            ]]>
        </kTAG_DEFINITION>
        <kTAG_SYNONYMS>
            <item>kPREDICATE_VALID</item>
        </kTAG_SYNONYMS>
	</term>
    
    <!-- kPREDICATE_LEGACY -->
    <term kTAG_LID="LEGACY" kTAG_NAMESPACE="">
        <kTAG_KIND>
            <item>:KIND-PREDICATE</item>
        </kTAG_KIND>
        <kTAG_LABEL language="en">Legacy version</kTAG_LABEL>
        <kTAG_DEFINITION language="en"><![CDATA[This predicate indicates that the object of
        	the relationship is the <i>former or legacy</i> choice, in other words, the
        	object of the relationship is <i>obsolete</i> or <i>not in use</i>. This
        	predicate will be used in general to <i>record historical information</i>. The
        	scope of this predicate is similar to the <tt>PREFERRED</tt> and <tt>VALID</tt>
        	predicates, except that in this case the legacy choice <i>might not be
        	invalid nor deprecated</i>: it only means that the object of the relationship
        	<i>was used in the past</i> and the subject of the relationship is currently
        	used in its place.
            ]]>
        </kTAG_DEFINITION>
        <kTAG_SYNONYMS>
            <item>kPREDICATE_LEGACY</item>
        </kTAG_SYNONYMS>
	</term>
    
    <!-- kPREDICATE_XREF -->
    <term kTAG_LID="XREF" kTAG_NAMESPACE="">
        <kTAG_KIND>
            <item>:KIND-PREDICATE</item>
        </kTAG_KIND>
        <kTAG_LABEL language="en">Cross reference</kTAG_LABEL>
        <kTAG_DEFINITION language="en"><![CDATA[This predicate indicates that the subject of
        	the relationship is <i>related</i> to the object of the relationship. This
        	predicate does not represent any specific type of relationship, other than what
        	the edge object attributes may indicate. The scope of this predicate is similar
        	to the <tt>XREF-EXACT</tt> predicate, except that the latter indicates that the
        	object of the relationship can be used in place of the subject, while in this
        	predicate this is not necessarily true.
            ]]>
        </kTAG_DEFINITION>
        <kTAG_SYNONYMS>
            <item>kPREDICATE_XREF</item>
        </kTAG_SYNONYMS>
	</term>
    
    <!-- kPREDICATE_XREF_EXACT -->
    <term kTAG_LID="XREF-EXACT" kTAG_NAMESPACE="">
        <kTAG_KIND>
            <item>:KIND-PREDICATE</item>
            <item>:kKIND_TERM_SYMMETRIC</item>
        </kTAG_KIND>
        <kTAG_LABEL language="en">Exact cross reference</kTAG_LABEL>
        <kTAG_DEFINITION language="en"><![CDATA[This predicate indicates that the object of
        	the relationship <i>can be used in place of</i> the subject of the relationship.
        	If the predicate is found in both directions, one could say that the two
        	<i>vertices are identical</i>, except for their formal representation.
        	The scope of this predicate is similar to the <tt>XREF</tt> predicate, except
        	that the latter only indicates that both vertices are related, this predicate
        	indicates that they are <i>interchangeable</i>.
            ]]>
        </kTAG_DEFINITION>
        <kTAG_SYNONYMS>
            <item>kPREDICATE_XREF_EXACT</item>
        </kTAG_SYNONYMS>
	</term>
</terms>