<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<terms>
    <!-- NAMESPACES -->
    
    <!-- Default namespace -->
    <term kTAG_LID="">
        <kTAG_KIND>
            <item>:TERM-KIND-NAMESPACE</item>
        </kTAG_KIND>
        <kTAG_LABEL language="en">Default namespace</kTAG_LABEL>
        <kTAG_DESCRIPTION language="en">This namespace groups all default terms of the ontology, these are the
            elements that will be used to build the ontology itself.
        </kTAG_DESCRIPTION>
     </term>
    
    <!-- IDENTIFICATION ATTRIBUTES -->
    
    <!-- kTERM_LID -->
    <term kTAG_LID="LID" kTAG_NAMESPACE="">
        <kTAG_LABEL language="en">Local identifier</kTAG_LABEL>
        <kTAG_DESCRIPTION language="en">This attribute contains the local unique identifier. This value represents
            the value that uniquely identifies an object within a specific domain or namespace. It is by definition
            a string constituting the suffix of the global identifier.
        </kTAG_DESCRIPTION>
        <kTAG_SYNONYMS>
            <item>kTERM_LID</item>
        </kTAG_SYNONYMS>
    </term>
    
    <!-- kTERM_GID -->
    <term kTAG_LID="GID" kTAG_NAMESPACE="">
        <kTAG_LABEL language="en">Global identifier</kTAG_LABEL>
        <kTAG_DESCRIPTION language="en">This attribute contains the global unique identifier. This value represents
            the value that uniquely identifies the object across domains and namespaces. This value is by definition
            a string and will generally constitute the object's primary key in full or hashed form.
        </kTAG_DESCRIPTION>
        <kTAG_SYNONYMS>
            <item>kTERM_GID</item>
        </kTAG_SYNONYMS>
    </term>
    
    <!-- kTERM_UID -->
    <term kTAG_LID="UID" kTAG_NAMESPACE="">
        <kTAG_LABEL language="en">Unique identifier</kTAG_LABEL>
        <kTAG_DESCRIPTION language="en">This attribute contains the hashed unique identifier of an object in which
            its native identifier is not related to the global identifier. This is generally used when the
            native identifier is a sequence number.
        </kTAG_DESCRIPTION>
        <kTAG_SYNONYMS>
            <item>kTERM_UID</item>
        </kTAG_SYNONYMS>
    </term>
    
    <!-- kTERM_SYNONYMS -->
    <term kTAG_LID="UID" kTAG_NAMESPACE="">
        <kTAG_LABEL language="en">Synonyms</kTAG_LABEL>
        <kTAG_DESCRIPTION language="en">This attribute contains a list of strings that represent alternate
            identifiers for the hosting object. Synonyms do not have any relation to the namespace.
        </kTAG_DESCRIPTION>
        <kTAG_SYNONYMS>
            <item>kTERM_SYNONYMS</item>
        </kTAG_SYNONYMS>
    </term>
    
    <!-- CLASSIFICATION ATTRIBUTES -->
    
    <!-- kTERM_CATEGORY -->
    <term kTAG_LID="CATEGORY" kTAG_NAMESPACE="">
        <kTAG_LABEL language="en">Category</kTAG_LABEL>
        <kTAG_DESCRIPTION language="en">This attribute is an enumerated set that contains all the categories to
            which the hosting object belongs to.
        </kTAG_DESCRIPTION>
        <kTAG_SYNONYMS>
            <item>kTERM_CATEGORY</item>
        </kTAG_SYNONYMS>
    </term>
    
    <!-- kTERM_KIND -->
    <term kTAG_LID="KIND" kTAG_NAMESPACE="">
        <kTAG_LABEL language="en">Kind</kTAG_LABEL>
        <kTAG_DESCRIPTION language="en">This attribute is an enumerated set that defines the kind of the hosting
            object.
        </kTAG_DESCRIPTION>
        <kTAG_SYNONYMS>
            <item>kTERM_KIND</item>
        </kTAG_SYNONYMS>
    </term>
    
    <!-- kTERM_TYPE -->
    <term kTAG_LID="TYPE" kTAG_NAMESPACE="">
        <kTAG_LABEL language="en">Type</kTAG_LABEL>
        <kTAG_DESCRIPTION language="en">This attribute is an enumerated set that contains a combination of data
            type and cardinality indicators which, combined, represet the data type of the hosting object.
        </kTAG_DESCRIPTION>
        <kTAG_SYNONYMS>
            <item>kTERM_TYPE</item>
        </kTAG_SYNONYMS>
    </term>
    
    <!-- kTERM_CLASS -->
    <term kTAG_LID="CLASS" kTAG_NAMESPACE="">
        <kTAG_LABEL language="en">Class</kTAG_LABEL>
        <kTAG_DESCRIPTION language="en">This attribute is a string that represets the referenced object's class.
            This attribute is used to instantiate the correct class once an object has been retrieved from its
            container.
        </kTAG_DESCRIPTION>
        <kTAG_SYNONYMS>
            <item>kTERM_CLASS</item>
        </kTAG_SYNONYMS>
    </term>
    
    <!-- kTERM_NAMESPACE -->
    <term kTAG_LID="NAMESPACE" kTAG_NAMESPACE="">
        <kTAG_LABEL language="en">namespace</kTAG_LABEL>
        <kTAG_DESCRIPTION language="en">This attribute is a reference to a term which represents the namespace
            of the current object. The object local identifiers must be unique within the scope of the namespace.
        </kTAG_DESCRIPTION>
        <kTAG_SYNONYMS>
            <item>kTERM_NAMESPACE</item>
        </kTAG_SYNONYMS>
    </term>
    
    <!-- DESCRIPTION ATTRIBUTES -->
    
    <!-- kTERM_LABEL -->
    <term kTAG_LID="LABEL" kTAG_NAMESPACE="">
        <kTAG_LABEL language="en">Label</kTAG_LABEL>
        <kTAG_DESCRIPTION language="en">This attribute represents the label, name or short description of the
            referenced object. It is a structure of type kTYPE_LSTRING in which the label can be expressed in
            several languages.
        </kTAG_DESCRIPTION>
        <kTAG_SYNONYMS>
            <item>kTERM_LABEL</item>
        </kTAG_SYNONYMS>
    </term>
    
    <!-- kTERM_DESCRIPTION -->
    <term kTAG_LID="LABEL" kTAG_NAMESPACE="">
        <kTAG_LABEL language="en">Description</kTAG_LABEL>
        <kTAG_DESCRIPTION language="en">This attribute represents the description or definition of the referenced
            object. It is a structure of type kTYPE_LSTRING in which the description can be expressed in
            several languages.
        </kTAG_DESCRIPTION>
        <kTAG_SYNONYMS>
            <item>kTERM_DESCRIPTION</item>
        </kTAG_SYNONYMS>
    </term>
    
    <!-- kTERM_NOTES -->
    <term kTAG_LID="NOTES" kTAG_NAMESPACE="">
        <kTAG_LABEL language="en">Notes</kTAG_LABEL>
        <kTAG_DESCRIPTION language="en">This attribute represents the notes or comments of the referenced object.
            It is a structure of type kTYPE_LSTRING in which the description can be expressed in several languages.
        </kTAG_DESCRIPTION>
        <kTAG_SYNONYMS>
            <item>kTERM_NOTES</item>
        </kTAG_SYNONYMS>
    </term>
    
    <!-- kTERM_EXAMPLES -->
    <term kTAG_LID="EXAMPLES" kTAG_NAMESPACE="">
        <kTAG_LABEL language="en">Examples</kTAG_LABEL>
        <kTAG_DESCRIPTION language="en">This attribute represents the examples or templates of the referenced
            object. It is a list of strings where each string represents an example or template.
        </kTAG_DESCRIPTION>
        <kTAG_SYNONYMS>
            <item>kTERM_EXAMPLES</item>
        </kTAG_SYNONYMS>
    </term>
    
    <!-- STATUS ATTRIBUTES -->
    
    <!-- kTERM_SEVERITY -->
    <term kTAG_LID="SEVERITY" kTAG_NAMESPACE="">
        <kTAG_LABEL language="en">Severity</kTAG_LABEL>
        <kTAG_DESCRIPTION language="en">
            <![CDATA[This attribute represents the severity or status level,
            it is an element of the following enumerated set:<ul>
            <li><tt>kSTATUS_IDLE</tt>: This code indicates no errors, this state can be equated to an idle state.
            <li><tt>kSTATUS_NOTICE</tt>: This code indicates a notice. A notice is an informative message that
            does not imply an error, nor a situation that should be handled; it can be considered as statistical
            data.
            <li><tt>kSTATUS_MESSAGE</tt>: This code indicates a message. A message is an informative message that
            is addressed to somebody, although it does not imply an error or warning, it was issued to a receiving
            party.
            <li><tt>kSTATUS_WARNING</tt>: This code indicates a warning. Warnings are informative data that
            indicate a potential problem, although they do not imply an error, they indicate a potential problem
            or an issue that should be addressed at least at a later stage.
            <li><tt>kSTATUS_ERROR</tt>: This code indicates an error. Errors indicate that something prevented
            an operation from being performed, this does not necessarily mean that the whole process is halted,
            but that the results of an operation will not be as expected.
            <li><tt>kSTATUS_FATAL</tt>: This code indicates a fatal error. Fatal errors are errors that result
            in stopping the whole process: in this case the error will prevent other operations from being
            performed and the whole process should be halted.
            <li><tt>kSTATUS_BUG</tt>: This code indicates a bug. Bugs, as opposed to errors, result from internal
            causes independant from external factors. A bug indicates that an operation will never execute
            as stated, it does not necessarily mean that it is fatal, but rather that the behaviour of an
            operation does not correspond to its declaration.
            ]]>
        </kTAG_DESCRIPTION>
        <kTAG_SYNONYMS>
            <item>kTERM_SEVERITY</item>
        </kTAG_SYNONYMS>
    </term>
    
    <!-- kTERM_CODE -->
    <term kTAG_LID="CODE" kTAG_NAMESPACE="">
        <kTAG_LABEL language="en">Code</kTAG_LABEL>
        <kTAG_DESCRIPTION language="en">
            This attribute represents the status code, it is a string or number that identifies the
            specific status or state.
        </kTAG_DESCRIPTION>
        <kTAG_SYNONYMS>
            <item>kTERM_CODE</item>
        </kTAG_SYNONYMS>
    </term>
</terms>
